the number one reason why a lot of
people do not like Amanda
seals is because Amanda seals spends way
too much
time talking about the people who don't
like Amanda seals so if you're
constantly people don't like me people
don't like me because of this people
don't like me because of that people
don't like me because I'm light-skinned
people don't like me because I'm raise
mdle class people don't like me because
I speak up people don't like me
because people don't like
me if that is constantly what you dwell
on that becomes your reality and the
reality of everybody who has eyes on you
on my body and they crystal clear I a
magic with these HS watch them disappear
uh-huh we going to rain drop something
my ear if you going name drop let's get
it
clear BBS just turn the water on big old
you never saw
before these
[Music]
[ __ ] now before I continue with this
video I want to thank this video sponsor
NX NX is a digital Healthcare platform
that makes it easy to get the expert
healthc care you deserve at every step
of your journey we all know that
everybody's journey is different so nurx
provides specific health care and
treatment that is personalized to you
and you only from birth control to
wrinkles to Dark Spot Treatment nx's
experts and licensed medical
professionals are here to address your
common health concerns I really want to
talk about their Dermatology Services
because me you guys know I've talked
about having combination skin more so
leaning towards drier skin I also deal
with hyperpigmentation and what I like
about nurx is when you go on the site
you're able to go ahead and address
their concerns and they also help guide
you into what brands are best for your
skin neurx offers more than 50
clinically proven dermatologist trusted
treatments for acne anti-aging and mesma
that work faster and are more effective
than over-the-counter product neurx
gives you the expert care that meets you
where you are so you can skip the making
appointments and waiting in line you can
complete a medical consultation any time
you'd like day or night 24/7 share your
skin history in a few photos and voila a
nurx provider licensed in your state
will review your health history and if
medically appropriate will prescribe
medication to you you'll get
personalized treatment and you'll get a
full year of unlimited messages to NX
thank you so much nurx again for
sponsoring this video taking control of
your health starts right here so go to
nx.com
Jessie woo nxx.com
Jessie woo and just so you get it right
it is
nx.com
Jessie woo okay to get started or click
the link Link in my description box to
go ahead and get started results May
Vary it's not offered in every state
medications prescribed only if
clinically appropriate consultation is
required thank you NX what's up guys
it's your
sister welcome back to my Chanel if
you're new here make sure that you
subscribe so you can join the black
women's tribe during black
women's it's so much going
on we're almost done with April y'all
what is May gonna be
mama you
know love you I love
you you know I love you
Mama Mama you're the queen of my heart
oh it's Mama's Day Mama's Mother's Day
is in May so
what you know what during black women's
I'm not one of your little friends month
how about
that so you know we gonna start May off
early okay during black women's I'm not
one of your little friends M okay shout
out to all the black women Mas out there
even though we're not in May yet but you
know what we're going to be celebrating
y'all all of May this week starts May
and honestly I don't know what day I'm
going to be able to upload this cuz I'm
so tired like I really want to get this
uploaded tomorrow it's Sunday night I
had the longest weekend like it was
great like I had the longest week
weekend but it started off with uh well
first of all I'm sorry hold on wait if
you're new here make sure that you
subscribe so you can join the black
women's tribe during black women I'm not
one of your little friends month okay um
also in June I am going to Kat colia
okay so if you want to join me for my
Kat Colombia trip make sure that you go
to
w.net uh and sign up all the information
will be there do not email my
partnership email CU you're not going to
get answered all of the information is
on w.net and there is a contact us box
if you submit your questions there
you'll be able to get a response um what
else oh you know what y'all I went to a
Palmer's event
okay my weekend so my weekend was great
um I got to spend some time with Mr
Easter which was great um he's been
working like a dog I've been working
like a dog um so we spent a little bit
of time
I think one of the things I'm starting
to think about because I really I have
not been in a relationship in six years
is schedules like both of us I think
are
Workaholics and we work a lot uh I think
his line of work is more demanding than
mine because he works um he is a
producer he's a television producer so
working on shows like you have to be
there there and uh he's working on
multiple shows at one time right now so
he spread very very thin and so we just
went through a week where it was really
kind of rough like it was like our first
week where it was like wow this is kind
this is rough um we had a week where I
was gone for a minute when I went to New
York but it was I was gone for less time
he was gone for a minute and it was I'm
just starting to think damn like when
you're in a relationship with somebody
like you have to start thinking about
schedules and all that like damn like
how does that work I just really haven't
done this in so long so it's like
dang it's like a part of me that's like
oo is this going to work like have I
ever felt like that like you're you know
you're working a lot this person's
working a lot how do you how do you
balance that but I think we've been
doing a good job um we spent some time
together so that was great um I went to
a Mother's Day brunch will BLK which was
amazing they had their brunch at the
Garden Room here in Atlanta which is
great I didn't know that they had brunch
their brunch is amazing a May Zing if
you can ever go to the Garden Room for
their brunch please do um I borrowed my
my friend DJ cash his mom cash uh does
something called bom Tuesdays here in
Atlanta which this week we're going to
be I'm going to be hosting um I'm going
to be playing a new song out there it's
a I'm a piano song but I borred his mom
and she and her she and I wore the same
color we weree the same pink which was
crazy we didn't plan that I B his mom
and she was so so happy to go you know
his mom's Haitian like you know Haitian
M they they're going to one thing I love
about Haitian
moms you just show them that you're you
know just thinking about them and that
just means the world to them and she
just was so excited to come and spend
time with me and do the brunch she was
great it was great uh then I had to rush
I had to leave her at the brunch but
thank goodness his sister came so they
were able to stay at the brunch and have
a good time there was so much going on
they had so much food they had a henah
station a flower making station it was
crazy I went over to the convention
center for the natural hair show um and
I hosted the mayel booth that was crazy
shout out to myel for having me that was
crazy I didn't know that the natural
hair show was such a big deal like the
whole Atlanta was out there the whole
whole the whole Atlanta was out there it
was really amazing to be there and among
so many black women's during black
women's I'm not one of your little
friends M um so it was great um what
else then
today honestly I was so dog tired after
yesterday CU even after that I had like
other stuff I'm handling because I'm
actually shooting a video this week
and that's been a
lot that's been a lot and um
so today I was like I was so tired I'm
like I'm not going to do anything I'm
not doing anything today and then my
alarm went off and I had forgot that I
had a Palmer Event to go to my friend
cat she invited me and um Palmer now has
hair products which is crazy like I did
not know this I did not know that
Palmers had hair products I've used
Palmers my entire life like cocoa butter
their cocoa butter is everything I use
the different scents of their cocoa
butter like right now my favorite
moisturizers is the Palmer's Cocoa
Butter and Baseline their um their line
that i' I've showed you guys before with
the brown the brown bottle um but Palmer
is amazing and we did this plant
planting like they showed you how to be
like a plant mom to grow a plant they
showed us how it was just amazing it was
an amazing event shout out to cat and
shout out to the Palmer team and they
came to Atlanta and they didn't like
[ __ ] us it was a really really nice
event a really really nice event and I
got to speak with them marketing team
and that was a good conversation so
hopefully I get to do stuff with them
but in honor of me going to the Pomers
event I do want to send you guys um some
products from their hair care line so if
you are a member if you are a member the
first member to leave a comment under
this video I'll go ahead and contact you
and send you out some Palmer
products look y'all if the glove don't
fit you must equip
um all right y'all that's it let's go
ahead and get into this Amanda seals
interview on Club sh
Shay there's so much to
unpack so much to
unpack that I
actually was thinking about not making
this video because I think the internet
has become a very unsafe place to talk
about Amanda seal I really feel
like there's really no common ground
when it comes to talking about
her um it's either people really really
like her or people really really dislike
her which makes her a polarizing person
I guess um because of the because of the
emotions that she invokes in
others before I go into this interview I
want to say this and i' I think I've
said this before here and I'll say it
again
and the last month it's it's been really
disappointing to me to see this pile on
when it comes to Amanda seals um as far
as black Publications are concerned or
white-owned Publications that
are black people focused um seeing them
pile on her has been very disgusting to
watch it's been
sad to
watch say what you want about Amanda
seals Amanda seals has never cause
actual harm to anybody in our
community you may believe she's mean you
may believe she's difficult you may
believe she's a [ __ ] you can believe
whatever you may believe that she's a
diva the girl used to actually call
herself Amanda the
diva but to put multiple articles out
there
that will always forever be in our
search engines and for all and always be
attached to her name to put articles out
there that
are I mean for lack of better words just
degrading to her I think it was so
tasteless so tacky so harmful to just
put such a huge light on her it just
made her out to be
someone that's dangerous when she's not
she's not a dangerous person she's not
someone who is out here scamming people
she ain't out here scamming kids in
Haiti um she's not out here scamming
people you know that are looking for a
come up in the industry she's not out
here you know having people TR transport
pink powder she ain't a pink Powder Puff
girl you know what I mean like she's not
out here
harassing um her employees and creating
a toxic environment for her
employees
um she's
not someone who
has beat put their hands on
or or violated anyone's
body there's so many things that she's
not that to me just
should be enough to give her grace you
know what I'm saying and I just feel
like when it comes to black women the
way we just be so quick to throw away
black women to me it's just so wrong it
is so wrong I think it's important to
while acknowledging all the harmful
things that Amanda is not I think it's
important that we remember all the great
things that she is and I just want to
point up uh I just wanted to post a
couple clips of her using her platform
to address social issues she talked
about Haiti um she talks about Palestine
she talks about you know uh Dei and what
these lawmakers are doing to harmfully
roll back the times and you know make
black people the last in line again with
their policies and I think it's a it's
important that we just take a look at
some of these clips she even addressed
some of the Predators that we have in
the industry and her experience is there
Amanda is someone who's very um
knowledgeable she tells the truth she
tells her truth and I think that she has
been instrumental in helping people to
watch out for certain things in this
industry and I think that we need to
acknowledge that I could give y'all a
history
lesson on this happening forever in
America this right
here we've seen these
images history but what would be the
point because it's not history it's
happening now and we are living in a
place that is so [ __ ] backwards that
the past is the present but y'all want
to argue about
masks we don't have a shared focus and I
believe these demons have craw back to
the surface through the fissures of our
divide can do exactly what Medi Hassan
said he can do and listen to the
majority of the American people who have
made it abundantly clear that they want
to see a ceire they want to see
Palestinians no longer under the threat
of death for literally just being
Palestinian and we also want to see a
number of other things uh like Biden
actually just listening to us on the
subject of education on the subject we
want you know we really want to see we
want to see him stand up against the
Republicans that's what we really want
to see right we want to see an actual
difference that is a Chasm not a half
step because of things he's done and
things he hasn't done for Palestinian
people he's definitely lost my
confidence that's for damn sure I mean
at the the end of the day I am not in
any position to tell people how to vote
or where to vote or in terms of him
losing my vote ultimately none of these
politicians are really winning anyone's
vote they're just kind
of possibly getting it by nature of
choosing the lesser of two evils and if
I was a human being well I am a human
being and as I am a human being and I
was running for office I personally
would hate for someone to be voting me
because I'm the lesser of two evils that
means I'm still an evil right right so
so what should he do then if you were
the president what should he do if I
were the President right president seals
in third grade I said I would be the
first like female president of the
United States of America I'm sure K's
like
um I think on a basic note the president
can so here's some things that happened
this week that you should know about
Governor Ronda Satan wants to make it a
felony if you have an undocumented
immigrant in your home or car he also
introduced HB 999 and that is a bill
that if passed will remove all black
sororities and fraternities from college
campuses in Florida along with latinx
sororities and fraternities along with
gender studies feminist studies and
Jewish studies and more speaking of
Education Texas officials announced a
state takeover of Houston's nearly
200,000 student Public School District
yeah fascist long game getting control
of the schools South Carolina
Republicans proposed a bill that could
subject women who have abortions to the
death
penalty and Tucker Carlson and the Wall
Street Journal tried to blame the
Silicon Valley Bank crash on
diversity their thesis that they were
too focused on hiring diverse people to
see the money wasn't adding up the math
wasn't
mathing um now with all that being
said after watching this
interview and after watching how Amanda
seals has conducted
herself after this
interview I can tell you it is my
personal
opinion that the number one reason why a
lot of people do not like Amanda
seals is because Amanda seals spends way
too much time
talking about the people who don't like
Amanda
seals
okay okay whatever we dwell on whatever
we speak life
into that is our
reality okay so if you're constantly
people don't like me people don't like
me because of this people don't like me
because of that people don't like me
because I'm light-skinned people don't
like me because I'm raised mdle class
people don't like me because I speak up
people don't like me because
of people don't like
me if that is constantly what you dwell
on that becomes your reality and the
reality of everybody who has eyes on
you Amanda spends way too much time
dwelling on people people who don't like
her talking about people who don't like
her talking about why people don't like
her it's too
much it's too
much that is
exhausting I remember there was a time
when I was constantly going back and
forth with a certain group of Haans all
the time the HMI that's what we'll call
them the HMI and there will be people in
my comments that would say Jess like you
need to stop focusing on this group over
here who doesn't [ __ ] with you we love
you we love
you and I remember I would start seeing
those type of comments
especially
um I had a big blowout last year with
and I'm spoken about it before but big
BL out with this DJ who I never spoke to
never talked to never met whose team I
never spoke to never
met there was a guy who literally told
me that he grew up with my father's
family and knew my father in Montreal
Canada you'd even tell me man like I
grew out my beard just like your father
your father was a legend in these
streets you know I've told you guys when
my father was out there doing in the
Montreal streets and one of the reasons
why I always have been transparent with
my father's battles is because I knew
very early on I would see how people
would find your tea and expose you so to
me you were never going to
expose my daddy's being a crackhead to
me you were never going to make content
out of that I was always going to be
transparent about that cuz nobody was
ever going to make me feel ashamed about
that ever but this man would coming me
and even even tell me don't [ __ ] with
the HMI they're crazy they're this
they're that and would always ask me to
do event and finally last year he asked
me to do an event and I agreed flew out
to New
York went to the
hotel I go to check into my hotel
there's no hotel room under my name I
call him the hotel room was under
someone else's name some random guy's
name apparently the event they didn't
they couldn't afford the room at the
Marriott but it took me three hours of
going back and forth with him
and him kind of gaslighting me hanging
up calling me back hanging up oh wait
I'm I'm handling I'm I'm handling I'm
handling come to find out the room was
under someone else's
name because that person's that person
had a Marriott discount so the event
person couldn't even afford a Marriott
room right then it was oh pay for your
own room
no
no so first of all you were going to
have me
stay in a room that belongs to some man
that I don't
know mind you we've all seen stories
about women being trafficked women being
killed women being assaulted like so
basically you were setting me up to get
assaulted basically and I still Overlook
that like come fix this [ __ ] I still
Overlook that and I wait for three hours
after 3 hours I [ __ ] leave and I get
on a flight back
home and it's oh she's a diva she's a
[ __ ] she's difficult she's this she's
that this guy go goes on the internet
the DJ guy goes on the internet never
telling the full story of no we didn't
have a room for her right but it's so
funny as I tell this story I'm
remembering now I don't think I've ever
said this but as this was going down I
was at a restaurant called apartment 4B
here in Atlanta and I was there with
Issa Ray's team because we were working
on the second the second season of the
chat [ __ ] podcast for rap [ __ ] on HB y
so I'm going back and forth with these
idiots
online you know that's why the Haitian
that's why the culture don't [ __ ] with
you and I was like yeah well [ __ ] the
culture I don't care oh she said [ __ ]
Haitians never said
that never said that but yeah [ __ ] the
culture who would actually send me to a
room that does not belong to me and put
me in danger like that and then get
online and not be transparent about that
but talk about me as if like you know me
as if you've talked to
me not acknowledging what you did to me
you know what I'm saying and I'm putting
up receipts and still the HMI Haitians
are [ __ ] you [ __ ] you we don't [ __ ] with
you and I'm like all right well [ __ ]
y'all I don't [ __ ] with y'all either oh
you don't [ __ ] with haian it's okay for
them to tell me don't [ __ ] with me but
the minute I say I don't [ __ ] with them
it's a problem
right
but I say all that to say there were
people that were like girl stop [ __ ]
with this group of people stop
acknowledging this group of people
because you have all these people over
here who do love you who do [ __ ] with
you who do support
you
and I started just to think about how
exhausting that is for people who do
support me for them to see me always
going back and forth with these
people watching
Amanda triggered that for
me like the fact fact that this is
almost always what I see with this woman
is that she's always acknowledging and
going back and forth with people who
don't like her who are committed to not
liking her she's mentioning people that
we the public don't know public don't
care about and how they don't like her
and it's
like that is why a lot of people don't
like you it's not just that this and
that has happened is the fact that you
keep shining a light to the fact that
there are people out there who do not
like you and I'm I'm not saying that as
a way to diminish her experiences
because her experiences are her
experiences especially in this industry
a lot of folks I'm sure there's a lot of
[ __ ] that Amanda didn't talk about in
this three-hour
interview
but her experiences have her experiences
and I'm not here to invalidate that
but when you keep talking about people
not liking you that opens the door for
people to continue to not like
you okay to continue to not like you it
opens a door for that so we've got to
get to the point
where we stop acknowledging
that we stop sh shining a light on that
because that now is your reality because
that's all you acknowledge or seemingly
acknowledge at least to everybody who
has eyes on you going back to the fact
that when everything was happening with
the DJ online that I was actually in a
restaurant with issa's
Team Gea who works at uh issa's company
who hired me for the chat [ __ ] podcast
her and and and and and my Zach and you
know other people that were there that
were part of the work we're doing they
were all like just like because they
read the post and they're like yo this
is this is not you we know who you are
we know what it's like working with you
we know you are a pleasure you are a
pleasure to work with you have been
amazing to work with and it's like while
people were online dogging me out in
person I was with these people and I was
crying because it was like I think
sometimes you really want everybody to
like you you want the world to see you
how people who actually know you you
want the world to see you that way but
unfortunately that's just not the
reality of most of us okay a lot of us
will be unliked especially by people who
have never interacted with us that's
just the reality especially if you have
a following especially if you have a
following if you're someone like me who
does commentary shoot if you go on my my
last video people are people are
dragging me cuz I won't I I I I'm biased
for porsa Williams you know what I'm
saying like just because I keep saying
yo guys her and Fallon were not friends
and y'all are like well but she still
slept with her husband never said she
didn't my point is they were not friends
you have Fallon in an interview saying
they were not
friends people will not like me because
of that cuz now I'm so supporting
someone sleeping with someone's husband
you know what I mean like it is what it
is I can't fight that battle if they
don't like me they don't like
me everybody is
not required to like
you that's something I really I had to
realize everybody is not required to
like you however it has been my reality
that in spite of people not liking me
I have still been able to pay all my
bills for the last seven years off of me
liking me enough to believe in my talent
and to use it somebody not liking me has
not stopped me from paying a phone bill
somebody not liking me has not stopped
me from buying this home somebody not
liking me has not stopped me from buying
them two cars in my garage somebody not
my my smart fridge downstairs like and
that's not me being
arrogant or showing off CU I don't even
like to tell you guys how much money I
make and I I will never say that because
money comes and goes you can make money
today and literally be be broke and on
your ass tomorrow that's the way of the
world
right
but people not liking me has not stopped
me from
thriving and living my life
the way I choose to live it and I really
want Amanda to understand
that people don't have to like you you
better make sure that you like you you
better make sure that every day when you
wake up in the morning you like what you
see you better make sure in the morning
when you wake up that you like yourself
enough that you commit to using whatever
your your god-given talent
is whether it be being a Creator whether
it be being a manager at at the local
grocery store whether it be being a bank
teller whether it be being a a car
technician whatever whatever your gift
is in this life you better make sure
that you like yourself enough to commit
to doing what you need to do to thrive
in this life in spite of somebody at
work not liking
you we all have people at work that
don't like us
we've all like raise your hand if you
have Folks at work that don't [ __ ] with
you before I had a platform I I work in
Corporate
America my last Corporate America job I
was the I was it was only three people
three black people in that company and I
I experienced a lot of
racism I got fired from that job that
still didn't stop me from doing
what I was set in this world to do and
finding my purpose in this life so I
just I don't know I feel like I'm
ranting but I really want Amanda to get
to the point where people's opinion of
her people not liking her is no longer a
subject let this be the last time that
this is a subject I want to talk about
Shannon sharp for a moment throughout
this interview
right I feel
like and and I'm saying this as someone
who has not Faithfully watched Shannon
sharp
interviews there was a point in my life
where Shannon sharp and uh skit bis and
Stephen A Smith did have me in a choke
cold like I was a I was a football head
and I used to enjoy watching Shannon
sharp dissect the game of football like
I think he is a genius when it comes to
sports especially football and you know
guy stuff he's very entertaining I feel
like Shannon sharp is a very handsome
man to look at some of y'all going to
disagree with me
but I think Uncle Shan is very
attractive he's very enjoyable to watch
in my opinion right um however watching
him in the Cat Williams interview I
remember in my video I said Shannon
sharp doesn't have great interviewing
skills and a lot of like red pill guys
found themselves in my comments telling
me you know to stay in the kitchen I
don't know what I'm talking about you
know he he's not it's not to get
interview his platform is not to to
interview the person is to give the
person a space to speak and it's like
bro this is a podcast it's a podcast if
you don't want to call it a interview
it's still a podcast in a podcast folks
are going back and forth it
becomes an interview because you're
going back and forth with folks and
you're you're it's you're debating
something you're having a discussion at
the very least and and I just felt like
when he interviewed or when he had Cat
Williams on his podcast Cat Williams did
such a good job at disarming him he
would give him compliments and often
times it were backhanded compliments
that spoke to uh Shannon's inability to
speak clearly that kind of to me lowkey
called them a a shuger and a dver there
were times when I feel like he called
Shannon ugly like you know but he didn't
do it outright
Williams is just really cool with his
words and but he was able to disarm
Shannon and just interview himself
basically like he was able to overtake
the interview and just interview himself
then you had Mo'Nique and I feel
like Shannon sharp saw the commentary
about Cat Williams and him not really
giving Cat Williams much push push back
and even cat said before he went on the
show that he would watch Shannon let
other comedians come on his platform and
say whatever
so I feel like after the Cat Williams
interview Shannon saw that criticism and
was like okay no I do have to push back
I do have to ask more questions and I
kind of saw an uptick in that with
Mo'Nique but even with Mo'Nique Mo'Nique
was still able to disarm him she would
compliment him like you know she would
she just was really good at disarming
him and telling a joke here and there
and she was able to get to say what she
wanted to say and and and steal the
ation back to the subjects that she
wanted to focus on
um and yeah I feel like I watched the
Lil ra interview a little bit but Lil ra
the Lil ra interview was not that
entertaining to me um but yeah he's had
Chris Brown on there he's had a lot of
big names on his platform um quo no was
it quo or offset recently he's had a lot
of people on there it just feels like
the comedians are the ones that go more
most viral and I really think that it's
because as comedians they just have a
gift they have a knack for telling
stories right but anyway Shannon sharp
is not
sharp I think outside of sports he's
just not sharp he's not well-versed he's
not educated in a lot of subject
matter which is why I think he needs to
do a better job at preparing himself for
his guest the fact that one of the first
things that he asked a man
or or S to Amanda you know within the
first couple minutes of the show I think
the first 10 minutes so your mama's
white why we not researching
that and I think he said that to her
twice your mom so your mom is
white she mom's not
white Amanda has two black parents I
believe her father is African-American
and her mom is grenad in two black
parents okay
I'mma need Shannon not so sharp to make
sure that his team prepares him for his
interviews okay one thing Shannon is
very good at is a beautiful introduction
any time you watch the Shannon sharp
interviews his introduction amazing how
he introduces his
guests amazing how he introduces his
guests like I think whoever writes his
introductions needs to write them for
for like all the big talk shows all the
award shows like whoever is doing that
writing is amazing but I need his team
to better prepare him he wasn't prepared
to talk about a lot of these things okay
um
the subject matter where Amanda was
talking
about um her teacher spreading
misinformation you know and her teacher
chastising her for her correcting her
and and and Amanda was the only black
child in the room and you have Shannon
well you know I mean where I come from
you know kids don't correct adults right
and a lot of people who are Shannon's
Age come from that era right but also I
would think
Shannon Shannon being the age that he is
would be able to look back at when he
was younger
and recognize that he too most likely
experienced racism from his white
teachers especially if he was in an
environment where there was a limited
amount of black students there's just a
certain gaze that you get as a black
child and when you have Amanda who
corrected her teacher and her teacher
chose to chastise her for it I think
Amanda even um mentioned the the teacher
lying on her about stealing you know
like and it was a white child that was
like no Amanda didn't steal and the
teacher was still like why you're still
going to get in trouble for this like
she was detailing
racism and when Amanda brought up Ruby
Bridges you know and uh they started
talking about children being racist and
Shannon was like well no I mean children
you know they're just kids and she's
like so so do you think the kids who
were spitting at and throwing rocks at
Ruby Bridges you don't think that they
were racist well you know they're
learning two things can be right at the
same no Shannon it's racism it's racis
racism is taught very early
on it is taught very early on which is
why when we look back at at people like
Ruby Bridges who's still alive this day
and we see her experience it was because
those kids were being taught racism by
their parents and when you hear Amanda
say I'm not understanding why at this
juncture you're trying to
defend someone that you don't know I'm
telling you the story I'm telling you
the story what happened with me and my
white
teacher I'm detailing racism to you why
are you trying to defend that and you
have Shannon saying well you know I
mean just cuz I'm bringing in another
point of view doesn't mean I'm trying to
be combat the the editing in that
segment was a little weird because it's
like he brought up the word combative I
felt like maybe she brought it up to
tell him hey you're being combative
about
this um but Shannon was being comb like
why are we defending racism just why
just it's why just why when I tell you
Dei cancellations are working so much so
that people that are Shannon Sharp's age
will defend racism it's it's really
crazy it was just really cringy to watch
and then um what else um I believe
Amanda was talking about you know just
some of her job experiences I think she
she talked about you know having a job
as uh at serus exm and that story was
wild and um I believe she talked about
like somebody else offering her a job
but they were upset at how she would
send out um
onew
answers and I think the one job was like
you know what hey we were G to offer you
this job but we just don't like the way
that you've been answering us you've
been giving these very short answers and
Shannon was like but you were answering
a yes or no question and she's like yeah
but they wanted me to and Shan was like
what they wanted you to shuck and job
for it and she's like yes right
um that part was a little cringe to me
but not just on Shannon's part but I
thought it was cringe on on on on
Amanda's part like correct me if I'm
wrong
but if you're going back and forth with
someone in email and they're asking you
yes or no questions
right what harm is there in yes please
or yes that's correct or yes I would
love to what harm is there in that that
don't mean you're necessarily shuing and
driving and you're just being
polite yes please absolutely I would
love
to that would be
great of course
yes what's the harm in
that just saying I don't think
everything has to be so
literal there are times when you can
just showcase a little more humanity and
that's something we're going to get to
later on when it comes to Amanda because
I feel like Amanda looks for a lot of
humanity in others but she doesn't
display it that's something we have to
discuss but um there's also a part too
where Shannon talked
about um the fact that a lot of times
folks have to wear a Halloween costume
and I was like damn I'm surprised nobody
cut that clip I thought that clip was
interesting but get out there and dance
[ __ ] okay yeah this is this is the part
finally I got an email that said you
know what we decided to go with somebody
else because by your your but people
need extra words like the normal way
that things are read so that I could
better protect myself like that may be
the truth but you don't got to tell it
right
now you know it and good for you right
hold that right hold that you don't got
to tell right right
um it may have been a yes or no question
but people need extra
words I lost a job because I was
answering in yes or no questions how you
lose a job if you answer yes or no
because you added because he they were
emailing me yeah asking me yes or no
questions okay and my responses were yes
yes and no and then finally I got an
email that said you know what we decided
to go with somebody else because by your
by your responses it seems like you're
not
interested well you say answer yes or
no so now you understand me it took us a
little bit but you're here so I'm so
they want you say yes I would love that
I'm sorry so now you understand me it
took us a little bit but you're here I'm
definitely going to be using that she
gave us a lot of good on Liners in there
definitely going to be using that but
again I just feel like although I don't
feel like that should be enough for you
to lose a job I do feel like okay if
somebody's asking you yes or no
questions yes please yes of course yes
I'd love to yes absolutely no no thank
you no but like what's the what's the
harm in
that why I feel like when somebody is
just so short with you when they're
giving you a like a a a short yes or
short
no that doesn't translate well
especially not in no email because
they're not face to face with you they
can't see your heart they can't feel
your spirit they can't see your tone so
it comes off very like
standoffish and I'm sorry if I'm if I'm
hiring
people I'm going to hire someone who
displays a little bit more Humanity than
that but for her she's like oh you know
people need extra words yeah we
do yeah it's just I don't
know etiquette it's just a nice thing to
do um but anyway let's continue so they
want you to say yes I would love to have
the job because I think this is amazing
opportunity for me and I just love this
company I think you
but get out there and dance [ __ ] but
Amanda and black people do it to each
other Amanda we had to conversation up
earlier what did we say if you
understand the rules no I didn't
understand the rules I'm just talking
then I didn't understand the rules I
didn't understand the learn so I was
saying the therapy helped you yes but
even still it's like understanding the
rules and like you know then you are who
you are like that ends up being in
conflict with each other so often you
know what I'm saying like you understand
the rules but you're like in order for
me to to like play this game I got to
like do a whole renovation of self
that's not going to be an
upgrade I don't
know I feel like my sister is constantly
like in this fight that doesn't have to
be there and like Shannon was saying you
know it can come off a little cringy but
if you listen to what he's saying he's
like Amanda if you understand the rules
like all of us like if you've gone to
school right remember when you were in
high school and they started teaching
you about how to apply for jobs and this
is how you write an email I don't know
how they do it now but this is how you
write a cover letter this is how you
answer emails this is your heading this
is your closing these are just courteous
things that I was taught in school how
to communicate when going back and forth
regarding a job opportunity
yes thank you so much for the
opportunity till this day till this day
when I get contacted to do uh
Partnerships with a brand or even like
some of the some of the ads that we get
here on YouTube going back and forth
thank you so much for the
opportunity it don't hurt me to say
that am I am I shucking and and Jobing
when I do that it it it hurts me none to
just say that and usually they remember
you for being that courteous because a
lot of people are just giving like all
right
cool just saying let's continue it's
just me really just trying to mask to
become um palatable to you but don't you
think realistically there are a lot more
people that dress in Halloween costumes
year round as opposed to just on that
day I do not want to be those people and
those are not the people that change the
world and that's what I'm here to do and
I literally went and got my masters
because rich boova on the campus of
purchas college stopped me and held my
hand because he was a psychic and he
would always do readings for people and
he just held my hand and was like well
you got to go get your Masters and I was
like God I thought I
would I don't know I I
just I don't know I just feel like
there's nothing wrong with that and like
how Shannon was saying don't you feel
there are a lot of people who do wear a
Halloween costume year round like he's
not saying that you have to act like
something you're not all the time but
there are times when you do have to just
bow down a little bit that's just part
of life that's part of playing the game
of life it's not just a Hollywood thing
it's just playing the game of life
people who are sweeter get more
honey you get more things with
honey you just do just being sweeter and
Kinder and showing just a little bit
more empathy you'll get more in life but
I wanted to talk about she had uh the uh
the story about bring on the funny I
think she was on a show with Chrissy
Teegan she said Jeff Foxworthy and she
was talking about how her experience
with Chrissy tigan tan was better than
her experience on insecure I thought
that was interesting um not to say that
I have anything negative to say about
Christy tan I don't but I thought that
was interesting and she talked about how
uh Jeff Foxworthy a white guy would step
in for her a lot at the job um
I thought that was interesting I it made
me sad that she found more solace in
non- Black
spaces I thought that was sad um later
on she talked about colorism a bit and
how it took her a while to really
understand how colorism worked you know
I
think as a light-skinned
woman colorism does really beat
light-skinned people's ass because a lot
of light-skinned people think there's
such a thing as reverse colorism and
when you hear her in the interview I
appreciated her saying no I had to
understand that there was not there's no
such thing and even me as a dark skinn
as a dark- skinned woman I've
experienced a lot of colorism growing up
I've been colorist to other dark skinned
women because I experienced so much of
it the other day I was on a panel
talking about coloris colorism and there
was uh another darkskinned woman on the
panel that was saying that even till
this day she struggles
with not looking at lighter skin as
Beauty versus her skin and I was like
damn do I still struggle with that I
think there's a part of me that does
still struggle with that because when
you look around light-skinned people
still do you know light-skinned biracial
uh ambiguous looking women or people
still get preferential treatment within
our community and outside of our
community in other communities as well
um she you know I think he brought up
her mama being white again because she
said something about her aunt being with
someone white I believe but that led uh
Amanda to talk about the fact that both
of her grandmother's a both I think both
of her grandmothers are great
grandmothers I think one grandmother and
one great-grandmother can't remember
what side of the family whether it was
her mom or her dad but she talks about
them being sexually violated and how it
led to her being her skin tone
um I think that that's a
really hot topic and if she were
speaking with someone with more range we
could have got more understanding about
her experience with colorism and her
experience with you know folks
automatically assuming that she is half
white because of her light skin and how
sometimes that can be
um harmful to her because I do feel
like we know all light-skinned people
aren't biracial right we know that but a
lot of times they're treated as such um
we're seeing right now with Beyonce
Beyonce did a whole video you know
showcasing her using her sacred products
and now the Discord is well she's not
totally black that's why she has that
type of hair mind you there are dark
skinned women I know dark skinned women
with the same hair texture as Beyonce
you know what I'm saying having certain
hair textures are not
always um attributed to someone's
Blackness there are Dominicans who are
no who are no black who have nappy
hair who have coiled hair right and they
go out of their way to strengthen it
because they are antiblack but their
hair ain't right so
that is a convers it's a loaded
conversation to have um this interview
is three hours long I have so many
thoughts I don't think I'm going to go
through all of
them but I will say just for the most
part just
Shannon
Shannon sharp is not so sharp and I
don't think that Shannon was the right
platform for Amanda to have certain
conversation but but before I go into
this next segment of me
talking I want to remind you all how
Amanda got on Club Shay Amanda went on
her
socials and she asked Shannon sharp I
believe this was back in January to
please interview
her I would love to do Shannon sharp
show I think it would actually be career
changing and not just for like my career
but the fact
that in showing that even when you keep
it a buck about things even when you
stand 10 toes down on issues that are
Global and political that even when you
align yourself with integrity and work
independently that you can still have a
fruitful career and I think that would
be career changing for a lot of folks
and for expanding the idea of what a
career in this industry actually can be
so Mr sh
if you were to have me on the show I
could make myself
available this was before all the M the
the the the black Publications and all
that was were slamming her you know even
back then she was talking about how
she's misunderstood and how she wants
you know to have a platform that she
thinks it is a safe place and all that
and mind you that just begs the question
too what do you see as a safe place what
do you see as a safe space because I
don't know I I to have the conversations
that Amanda wanted and needed to have I
don't think Club Shay was the place to
have those
conversations that to just to my to my
my opinion maybe some of you guys will
disagree but I don't think that was the
platform to have those
discussions okay um especially the
autism conversation my God
my God
just watching that segment alone was so
cringe and it is because again Shannon's
not so sharp but also Shannon was not
ready to have that conversation and a
lot of people are not ready to have a
conversation about neurodivergent people
and how they process things but also it
was kind of cringe to watch Amanda kind
of
lean into her neurod Divergence and her
autism
diagnosis and make that the reason for
why she behaves the way that she does
because if that's the case then I know a
lot of autistic
people if that's the case it's a lot of
us that are
autistic we all
artistic and I I listen and and I listen
I'm keeping it light I'm having a
lightweight lighthearted joke about that
during black women I'm not one of your
little friends month but let's be for
real let's be for real being
autistic is not an
excuse for not
having
empathy and I want to get to that when
it comes to Amanda I want to say
this initially watching this interview
Amanda got so much support and
predominantly so because people saw how
Shannon was just not the person for her
to have these conversations with Shannon
is not sharp at all outside of sports
right
and I kind of saw the internet turn on
Shannon
which while the interview is very cringe
I think it's kind of unfair to turn
Shannon into a villain here because
again Amanda asked to be on this man
show Amanda has seen this man and how he
conducts his interviews
now I don't I don't I refuse to believe
that she went on this platform without
doing her
research she went on there April 18th
she had plenty of time to do her
research right now I do feel like he
gave Amanda a lot more push back than
I've seen recently
but I think a lot of that came from
again from the commentary of people
watching the show like yo Shannon you
got to ask questions you have to you
know so I think a lot of it came from
that but the defending the defending um
racism comments
like you don't got to be on the Spectrum
to be brilliant cuz I feel like uh
Amanda said you know she felt she feels
that her father was autistic is autistic
as well and that he's brilliant and you
had Shannon say but I mean just cuz he
brilliant don't mean he on the Spectrum
like
he it's like it's almost funny
how I don't want to call this man dumb I
don't think he's dumb but it's just
almost funny
how it's almost funny how dumb he is let
just say it it's just almost funny how
dumb he is when it comes to these
subjects right but anyway let's talk
about her autism and and Her diagnosis
so when she went on the show she
revealed that recently she was diagnosed
to be autistic now also in the video too
she talks about how she's just a very
literal person and that is why she feels
a lot of people don't like her let's
listen you don't see the feelings of
catlyn Stark at the [ __ ] red wedding
until you watch the show because in the
writing it is just a series of events
that is part of my autism I speak in
directs I speak in linear spaces I speak
in literals that's part of the reason
why people don't like me neither because
I'm literal and I take things literally
so if you say to me I'm G be there at
five I'm like why you a't here at five
they're like well I'm at fiveish well
you should have said fiveish because I
was waiting for you at
five can I let me ask you this how old
were you when you got diagnosed no and
did you always feel that you was
different and you felt something was
wrong well what's today today is
Thursday the 18th so
42 and however many days until I I was
just recently diagnosed okay and this
came out of this situation because so
many black women who are autistic said
to me I see you you need to and I've
always thought that I've always thought
you can look at other interviews I have
mentioned before like I think I'm on the
Spectrum
because I'm an 80s baby this was not
really a part of the narrative right and
as we started seeing more about autism
and you start seeing shows about
different characters and I start
learning more like from people like
Holly Robinson
Pete
like this feels really like me
um but then you know I think sometimes
we're afraid to learn certain things
yeah so 60s and 70s baby just got whoi
and put to bed so two things right um
cuz I really want to go back to that
literal com comment that she made
but she talks about you know being
diagnosed with autism and um
how she also talks in the interview
about how
um getting diagnosed is a very hard
thing to do sometimes because of the
racism in the medical field and I think
that we really do need to take a pause
and think about what she was talking
about when she talked about that again
Shannon sharp wasn't the person to have
that conversation with as a black woman
during black women's I'm not one of your
little friends month we know what black
women go through when it's time to give
birth we've seen recently uh a woman be
misdiagnosed with um what was that
influencer she was misdiagnosed
with beauty influencer Jessica Petway
died of cervical cancer following
misdiagnosis the 36-year-old died a year
after being diagnosed with stage three
cical cervical cancer which doctors
originally said was just fibroids
okay so we know as black people
that the medical industry is not an
industry that is favor favorable for
black people ES especially black women
our bodies are still so very
misunderstood I saw recently how uh um
uh what's the girl blame it on my own my
Victoria Monet she was talking about how
you know so many people were talking
about how thick she looked at Coachella
cuz that ass was that ass that ass was
sitting and she came forward and she
said hey guys so I recently found out
that I have PCOS she gained so much
weight if you remember her around the
Grammys in February to now in April like
she gain it looks like she gained a good
20 pounds and that's a short amount of
time to gain weight I was just having a
conversation over this weekend with some
folks about my body and how a lot of
times like I will juice for a couple
days just to keep my weight down and
it's the conversation was what what you
what weight are you trying to lose what
weight are you keeping down and it's
like bro our bodies don't function all
the same it is very easy for me to gain
weight and uh I remember asking my
doctor if I had PCOS and she was telling
me that I should go to a nutritionist
and do this and that it wasn't just
something easily that she could diagnose
right and so I'm thinking about if
something like that is so hard to
diagnose imagine ADHD
imagine
[Music]
um autism you know something that I know
I've never been diagnosed for but a lot
of you guys sometimes will notice how
how how ashy my hands are something I've
never said to you guys sometimes my skin
starts to split and it will bleed and
that is eczema I have extreme eczema on
my hands and it's something that I
developed in the last couple years and
finding different moisturizers finding
different you know um products that are
best for my skin has been was an issue
for me for a long time but I think I'm
there I think I'm good I'm getting
better like this was the first winter
season that I didn't see any splits in
my skin yes it will get like sometimes
my hands will get inflamed especially
this hand it will get inflamed and it
will get so Rocky like it will feel like
my hand will feel like sand you know um
our bodies are are not a monolith okay
black bodies are not a monolith um being
diagnosed is is for a lot of things cost
a lot of money it's very costly and so I
think that that's what Amanda was
speaking to when she was talking about
getting her autism diagnosis she kind of
talked about the racism in the medical
field in the
interview now
post the interview Amanda [ __ ] this up
like watching
Amanda [ __ ] up her support in less than
24 hours has been astonishing to me
because when she spoke up about having
autism so many people were like oh my
gosh you have a autism I feel seen oh my
gosh you have this I feel seen you know
what I mean there's been some of you
when I talk to you guys about my HPV
scare some of y'all were in the comments
and even till this day the other day I
was telling you guys I felt a lot of
pain and there was some of y'all in the
comments just you need to go check maybe
it's maybe you know it's your cix like
you know what I mean like y'all be
feeling seen right and so she was for
the support of people supporting her
like wow I'm autistic too I feel seen
I'm divergent This is my experience so
many people were rallying behind her and
then she gets on live and she does this
uh they cut out at the end he was asking
no I have not been clinically diagnosed
by a doctor because I'm not paying
$10,000 to do that and most people will
tell you that at this age you don't need
a clinical diagnosis in the in that
sense and I think that's the other thing
it's
like we are so um condition here in this
nation
to um really only consider something in
one kind of way and uh I will get back
to that and this clip of her from her
Instagram live was something that was
going viral on on on on Twitter threads
everywhere and so Blog start to pick it
up and you have baller alert who posted
it right shade room posted every blog
posted it right right because hello you
said you were diagnosed but in this live
you're saying you self diagnosed right
and so people are like well what what
what is it like so do you really have
autism or not like what what is it and
so you have people posting and then she
saw the baller alert post so now the
Class Act baller alert yet another black
space because there is such a dedicated
effort to
degrade me and defame me it is beyond my
scope of comprehension wants to suggest
that because my autism diagnosis did not
come from a clinician that it is not
valid what's not valid is people
speaking on things that they don't know
about and my autism diagnosis is not for
you all to discuss it's not up for your
debate and anyone who is speaking on or
trying to invalidate uh diagnosis that
comes outside of a CL
is only repe revealing that they
actually don't know anything about
autism diagnosis or Autism so I just
want to once again um thank you all for
the love and this is further proof of
why we as black people particularly in
in Black media spaces we are and this
was baller alerts response like girl
we're just posting what what you
posted we're just posting what you
posted we're not
like watching her go off on baller alert
was crazy to me because I'm like girl
they're just posting what you said
what's the harm and just saying hey guys
you know based on my symptoms throughout
the years I self- diagnosed myself right
what's the error what's the problem in
just saying that we're going on these
Rants
and now we're saying that Shannon sharp
was undering you and he was committed to
not understanding
you this is the same guy who asked
Amanda seals for a hug and she said no
this was at the top of the
interview he even mentioned her coming
in and her being so tense you know like
and asking if this was a safe space and
he's like yo like we're I want to make
you feel welcome like you know like
you're good like
just going off on sh like I I watched
her
spend the day that the interview dropped
and the entire weekend going off on
Shannon sharp and again he may not be
the brightest but turning him into a
villain and then like turning the public
into villains because they're
questioning what you said when you were
on the podcast you said you were
diagnosed when you tell folks that
you've been
diagnosed they're just automatically
assuming your doctor diagnosed
you or your psychiatrist diagnosed you
right what is the problem in just saying
hey guys based on my symptoms you know
my mother you know sharing some things
with me about my upbringing and all the
symptoms that I display to her cuz she
touched on that she said that her mom
saw a lot of autistic syp Syms in her as
a child what's the problem in just
clarifying that and saying I self I self
diagnose I'm sorry for the
confusion what's the problem in just
admitting that you
misspoke could that be one of the
reasons why people don't like you is
that you have a hard time just
acknowledging when you make a misstep we
all do it we all make mistakes it's okay
to just say hey guys I
misspoke you're a you're a woman of very
many
fancy multi- syllabled
words so people are expecting you
to give us information and give it to us
accurately that's all and so when you
post things like this is you're losing
support you're losing support and then
when you say things like well I wasn't
going to pay
$10,000 I get it it's very expensive
like I get it it's very expensive but
again you know you have everyday women
who are looking to you like yeah it's
very expensive like you know to get a
diagnosis it's this it's that I've seen
so many women come forward and talk
about how it's just $3,000 just for
doctor's visits when it comes to autism
I get it at the end of the day though
Amanda you've been in the business for
over 30 years so a lot of people are
looking at you and assuming $10,000 is
nothing to
you especially during the days of
insecure where you're on this hit show
for five
years you've had two HBO uh specials
you're always on tour so people you know
with the smart funny and black so people
are assuming $10,000 is nothing for you
just saying just saying what is the
problem with just clarifying
yourself like that this is gaslighting
it's gaslighting okay and I think that
that might be one of the reasons why
people don't [ __ ] with
you it's just your inability to
acknowledge when you misstep it's okay
to say you know
what I miss I mised I misspoke I
misspoke and let's move forward let's
move forward
um it was cringy
watching well Shannon sharper has been
very nice about Amanda even despite a
lot of the [ __ ] that I've seen her say
about him online he hasn't said anything
negative about her I saw this clip where
he talked about her and it was him
Gilbert Arenas and ooo talking about you
know her being on the podcast he was
very happy about her being on the
podcast but then you had these men
talking about well this is why she ain't
got no man back she
she like can I have a
hug and then she was
cool I think a lot of things
that and people like I was trying to
invalidate her experience no I wasn't
it's the same thing I told Mo'Nique when
Monique said I try you know I was trying
to get this role and Oprah told me to go
blah blah blah for right and she ended
up getting the role I said well Monique
did you ever think that they were
looking for a black heavy set Woman and
you two are probably the only two in
Hollywood and she said oh okay that
makes sense and so when she said the
white lady had uh her teacher I said
Amanda did it ever cross your mind
that I don't know where you from but
where I grew up
oo kids never corrected a parent or an
adult corrected yes it and that's what I
said I said I said Amanda did you think
maybe because you were a child even
though you were were right the mere fact
that a child corrected an adult now
maybe in today's time that's fine maybe
where in some place you grew up but I
don't ever remember being around being
in a
situation A Child couldn't even
interrupt an adult conversation you
couldn't pull on your parents or your
grandparents leg and say hey hey hey hey
hey I'm like huh no so that's what I was
saying I said maybe maybe Amanda it
wasn't racism Maybe was the fact that a
child was correcting an
adult but that was her experience that's
what that's what and like I said I mean
that's how she felt about it but I enjoy
the interview I enjoy talking to people
yeah I mean everybody and I try
not I do my research but I try to go in
as with as cleanest lady as I possibly
can because I don't want what someone
else has said about her to influence
what I think of her right yeah I'm GNA
come up I'm G ask the questions and then
at the end of the day hopefully she when
she sees it she'll be pleased with the
finished product but I ain't got no
problem with Manda seals she was great
uh she's very funny she has uh and I do
believe some of the people have done her
wrong and I think a lot of a lot of
because that's what you deal with we all
go through it dealing with me men or
women you're not dating them you're
dating their childhood their past
traumas that's what you that's what you
got to get past so I'm excited I was
excited to have her uh she was great she
taught me a lot of things uh but she oh
she's highly highly highly Highly
Educated she's real vers she can sing
she's a comedian she's a writer she oh
she's highly highly highly highly
educated she's real versed she can sing
she's a comedian she's a
writer is is she she married no she's
not married she's not married the same
day I mean yes I'm I'm I'm listening to
you list all the qualities that she has
and I'm just curious if if she was
married because that that I mean that
sounds like that that's a great cat for
someone yeah yeah yeah yeah no that
sounds like some flaws for
[Laughter]
some because
as educated as she is right yeah she
she's there's a standard of a man that
she's looking for right yeah if it's not
on the same educational level as her
she's gonna right down on and that is if
they're more educated than
her then they talking down to her these
are the type of women mind you these are
three men who are unmarried you have ooo
who I love you ooo is from the crib
they County Down always goingon to have
love for oo sinkle but baby how how many
baby M do you have how many children do
you
have
gilber are you married sh are you
married why is it that we don't put more
requirement on men to be
smarter and
stronger in order to be able to deal
with me women who are
intelligent who do have their own
personalities who own who they are like
why is it always a thing
where a woman being outspoken is seen as
threatening to a man's masculinity like
you men got to stop being [ __ ] we're
in
2024 like what like we need to start
sending men back to war that's that's
the problem these men got microphones
that's the problem unplug the microphone
un un plug the
microphone unplug the microphone and
send these [ __ ] back to
war unplug the microphone and send these
[ __ ] back to
war unplug the
microphone send them on the front
lines okay
I need I need you men to stop being
worried about a woman's masculinity just
because a woman is smart just because a
woman is outspoken that should not
threaten your masculinity if that turns
you into a [ __ ] we need to start
sending you [ __ ] back to
war y'all got to go back to
war okay matter of fact put Trump back
in office and send all these
[ __ ] back to
work yeah so y'all can shut the hell up
and leave us
alone this this it it's so tiring it's
so
tiring this conversation is so tiring
please shut up okay currently you're on
Kevin Hart's LOL network no you done
that that ended uh like two years
ago Kevin people's taking shots at Kev I
know Kev a little bit I don't but I
think he's I think he's great at what he
does I know he's an extremely hard
worker he puts a lot of time into his
craft uh and he's built a platform that
that tries to elevate
people oh Lord I think that's his goal
but I don't know that his staff has the
same fervor for that that he does okay
and mind
you Mo'Nique said this Mo'Nique
said the same exact thing that Kevin
Hart has a good heart Kevin Hart has
great intentions but there seems to be a
disconnect between Kevin and his
staff and I don't know that he's NE I
don't I'm saying this literally like I
don't know if he's if he's necessarily
empowered them to do that I literally
don't know I know that he voiced his
intentions to me but they were unable to
be carried out right and I have no hard
feelings KB um Kev looked out for me in
a
situation that
uh was you know life Nation tried to
like cancel my whole
tour and
and I had to call people I know that you
know got the juice right and and Kevin
answered the call that's unbelievable
and it was a time where I didn't have
other jobs so if I didn't do them shows
there was no money right because my man
made no money and he wasn't trying to
make no money so I was the only one
making the money right and I remember
sitting in my living rooms like staring
off into space and he came in because I
was quiet and if Amanda's quiet yeah we
in the problem and my man came my ex he
came in and was
like was you good and I was like no
because if I don't do these shows we
will not have money right for the bills
and so I really appreciate Kev um
because he didn't have to do that and he
did so In that clip we hear her talk
about how Kevin stepped in and helped
her out at a moment where Live Nation
was canceling her shows this was ding
her her money she was with a man who
also wasn't making any money so Kevin
Hart stepped in so the Shannon sharp um
social media team posted this clip of
that that that whole segment and there's
this clip going around of Amanda seals
going off on them because of it Kevin
Hart saved Amanda seals and her ex when
they weren't making
money you know I went on this show
because they said it was a safe space
and I I just I really
this I'm genuinely just disgusted like
this is this right here just this is
this is Club sh it's Club mess mess and
I went on this show because I saw the
way that it was a safe space for folks
and to do this right here the
messiness I you know it's just this is
what I mean about re redefining what a
black space means because this is not by
any means protecting black people but
get y'all for the
record what I did say because I know
you're not going to watch the interview
what I did say was that when Live Nation
tried to screw me out of my shows Kevin
Hart came to my support that's what I
did say and it's very important to point
out that this is not a situation where
my Amanda and her ex weren't making
money in Kevin Hart no I didn't get any
money from Kevin Hart what I got was was
the support of a fellow comedian and a
brother shame on
y'all I had to call people I know that
you know got the juice right and Kevin
answered the call that's unbelievable
and it was a time where I didn't have
other jobs so if I didn't do them shows
there was no money right because my man
made no money and he wasn't trying to
make no money so I was the only one
making the money right and I remember
sitting in my living rooms like staring
off into space and he came in cuz I was
quiet and if aand is quiet yeah we in a
problem and my man came my ex he came in
and was
like was you good and I was like no
because if I don't do these shows we
will not have money right for the bills
and so I really appreciate Kev um
because he didn't have to do that and he
did girl you you said it why are we
going off on Shannon like you said it
you said it and Kevin Hart is someone
whose name keeps popping up on the
Shannon sharp show I'm pretty sure his
Shannon sharp has reached out to Kevin
to come on the show because he's a hot
name on his
show so that's why they would post that
clip you said
it like
Amanda Amanda
you said it you might have not said it
word for word but you said it
another part of the interview that I
liked was Amanda talking about doing the
BET Awards and how two days prior I
think two or three days prior to the
actual show she was told she would have
to do the entire show from her home and
that it was her and her dude that she
was sleeping with at the time some Old
Reliable who was who was just happen to
come to her house that weekend because
they was G to hunch he turned into the
technician for the show and um she had
to do her own hair her own makeup and
this man was putting the wires together
and she talked about how he was outside
like you know bragging about saving the
BET Awards he like yeah let him tell it
he said he save the BET Awards and he
did girl he
did he did the same way we want to give
you your props for hosting
it because Amanda seals did a very good
job hosting the 2020 BET Awards during
the pandemic a fantastic job we didn't
know that it was her old reliable in the
background screwing up everything and
doing every like that's crazy that they
did that that way um she talks about
getting him a check for it which was
great but you know the same way we want
people to recognize us Amanda it's okay
to recognize that man that man did say
the awards both of you guys did so kudos
to both of you all right so I really
debated talking about this part of the
interview because I've worked with Issa
Ray you know Issa took me to Miami Amy
for abff two years ago I did two season
of rap shits Podcast chat [ __ ] I've had
such an amazing experience with issa's
Team Gea who's out there who hired me
for the podcast so I felt
like I would be very biased
and in my last video I saw so many
comments about your bias is showing your
bias is shown your bias is showing
especially when I was talking about F uh
not fad Porsche so I debated addressing
this
so here's what I'll say let's go back in
the interview and listen to Amanda talk
about her autism being the reason for
her being a literal person and not
someone who addresses a series of events
based on her feelings yeah when I
recount a story I want you to know no
this when of recount stories I don't I
very rarely include my feelings it's
never I felt that this person did this I
thought that this person did this it's
like reading Game of Thrones he's giv
the he's just giving you the sequence of
events you don't see the feelings of
catlyn Stark at the [ __ ] red wedding
until you watch the show because in the
writing it is just a series of events
that is part of my autism I speak in
directs I speak in linear spaces I speak
in literals I wanted to bring this up
because when I look at what she was
talking about with her experience on
insecure right and having to deal
with Vanessa issa's
publicist and her saying things like
Issa didn't protect me Issa didn't
Empower me I think about this moment in
the interview where she talks about
she's a literal
person Issa was being a literal person
to you too like have you guys ever been
around a female Capricorn and not to
make everything a sign but I have a
sibling who is a female
Capricorn when I tell you it's not about
feelings it's literal and when I look at
the way she said Issa communicated with
her I'm like so is that not how you said
you communicate you said you deal in
linear you don't deal with feelings you
don't deal with how somebody made you
feel you deal with linear that is
exactly how Isa Reay dealt with you
according to you according to her story
you're having this problem with her
publicist and Issa literally told you
this is none of my business y'all fix it
y'all get on a phone call y'all fix it
and don't bring it to my set point blank
period am I going to have issues on my
set no
great she spoke to you in a linear she
never said well you know what Amanda
this is how I feel about the
situation this is how Vanessa feels
about the situ she never did that
according to Amanda she dealt with you
very linear which according to you and
your autism that is how you understand
things that is how you explain things
that is how you see things so according
to you and your autism and how you
process information isay dealt with you
accordingly tell me if I'm
wrong not trying to be biased
here and as somebody who can
be very biased
because I love
isay love
isay I'm going to take this at literal
value Amanda said she deals
literally with things she doesn't
include her feelings she doesn't have to
share her feelings she doesn't think
about the which is why too when you
think about it it's like for a person
who's so literal because of their
autism you look for a lot of empathy but
you don't showcase empathy it's kind of
like the incident when she talked about
you know the Revolutionary [ __ ] right
you talked about the Revolutionary [ __ ]
on
set some guy in the background some guy
that works you know in the background of
the show and he did something she like
wow you you a revolutionary [ __ ] and he
was like I'm not a
[ __ ] and she said
okay right now
this guy goes and he tells someone above
them and now she's confronted and she's
reprimanded for using the word [ __ ]
which I thought was crazy because it is
insecure but also I do understand the
fact that every black person does not
like that word [ __ ] is not a word that
every black person
likes for many valid reasons right I
would have preferred for him to say you
know I'm not a [ __ ] please don't call
me that you know and I would have also
preferred for her to say you know what I
apologize right but even in that
situation you have her saying okay and
then you have her on the interview
saying I should have called him a [ __ ]
ass
[ __ ] you look for empathy Amanda and
and you don't have it you look for other
people to empathize with you but you
don't have that skill you don't have
that skill and again with the
Revolutionary [ __ ]
moment while I don't think he should
have went and got a third party
involved I strongly also do not think
that it should have taken a third party
to get involved for you to say I
apologize the moment he said I'm not a
[ __ ] I apologize about that I'm sorry
didn't mean to offend
you but remember you're literal
person you deal literally and so now
it's a problem that Issa is dealing with
you the way you're saying that you deal
with
things and let's keep it a
buck the whole vessa
thing I'mma just tell y'all where I
stand
if I know somebody don't [ __ ] with me
I'm not going to anything they have
going on I don't care if they're the
person doing the decorations I'm not
going back in December I got invited to
come to go perform at something down at
the barlay center for Haitian
Independence Day I looked at the
list I said oh no this DJ's been online
talking about me this DJ who was just
shaking his titties in my white C video
was in Michael Bron's comments talking
about me
not
going not going don't care I don't give
a [ __ ] if these [ __ ] are just
operating the life because they can wait
till I get on stage to turn it off don't
care don't
care and so to
me it was very obvious when you hear
this interview and I've heard her talk
about the Emmy the black Emmy party
before it's very obvious you and Vanessa
been had issues the fact that you went
to the party is wild to me and I
understand that somebody invited you but
I'mma say this too
right getting to the door and them
telling you you can't come in all I need
is one time for somebody to tell me some
[ __ ] [ __ ] I'm gone I'm
gone it's not that Pro it's not that
deep I don't got to shake my tail
feather with you [ __ ] tonight it's
okay it is okay the moment I get to an
event and I have one issue at the door
I'm G I'm the type of person if I get to
your event and I don't find parking I'm
leaving let alone me get to the door me
Park me tipto through Co through
Cobblestone well they were in La so it's
not Cobble but me tit toing and my Louis
Vuittons coming to the door and oh we
don't got you on oh okay cool I'm gone I
am leaving like I'm gone I'm gone
I'm done
quickly
quickly so to me there's just
a I find difficulty with understanding
why you want to be at somebody's event
that don't that clearly doesn't [ __ ]
with
you and it's just not just anybody this
is
somebody who has the
power to get you the [ __ ] thrown out and
again not saying it's right or
wrong not saying what happened to her
was right at the party but I'm just
saying if I don't [ __ ] with you and you
come to my [ __ ] [ __ ] I am getting you
escorted the [ __ ] out you know you know
what time we I don't [ __ ] with you you
come to my [ __ ] [ __ ] it's on and
popping security escort her the [ __ ]
out and we all know what happens when
security is escorting you out they are
like yo I forget I was at a I was at a
club I mean but I was I got into I was
getting into a fight like me and my
friends we was in the club brawling with
these girls who came to our table and
was trying to like muscle us out of our
section I go to like we're tussling I go
to grab a bottle literally I grabbed the
bottle
security next thing you know I'm getting
Jazzy Jeff out the damn
club like out the damn Club okay that's
how security operates
that's their
job to throw you the [ __ ] out and when
you hear her give the give the story
girl they told you several times not to
be in that damn Club not to be in that
damn party they told you several
times what is not
registering what is not
registering and
just and I don't want to do too much I
don't want to say too much on the Issa
part but I'm going say
this the Discord that I've seen
online because of Amanda's Issa story
has been very alarming to even elude now
I'm talking about the Discord to even
elude that Isa doesn't Empower other
black women is
ludicrous it's
ludicrous I've had three jobs at that
company
Gea who hired me black
woman Vanessa who is Issa ra PR that is
her best friend from college every time
you see Issa Vanessa is there and if you
look at Vanessa's Media company uh a
public relations company she has the top
clients in the
game just go look for
yourself the top
clients in the
game that is based on her and issa's
work they've worked together to do
extremely amazing things in this in this
industry they've they've empowered each
other and Issa
Issa the fact that wherever Issa has
gone she's taken Vanessa that's her
empowering her friend insecure was
written based on issa's group of friends
in
Sanford and she's hired so many of those
friends they're black
women chat [ __ ] was co-created by Serita
Singleton a black woman first episode
directed by shade Joseph a Jamaican
black
woman I can go on and on
isay and empowering black women those
two continents they meet they meet they
meet okay and while I'm sorry for
Amanda's
experience it begs a question well how
did they experience you Amanda every
everybody is not going to show up for
you exactly the way you want them to and
it doesn't make them a villain it
doesn't yes Shannon sharp is not so
sharp but it doesn't make him a villain
he did he wasn't coming for you in the
interview he wasn't interrogating you
that man is still learning he's still
learning and you asked him to be on his
platform knowing that this is not a man
who has the range to speak on the things
that you have the range to speak
on there has to come a time in life
where we just have to
own our shortcomings and that doesn't
make us a villain either it makes us
human it makes us
human I watched Amanda seals
burn every bridge in three
hours every bridge that you've built in
the last 30 years I watched you burn it
all in three hours and I saw you go
online and celebrate the fact that you
burned every bridge if that was your
goal with this interview you
succeeded and your behavior post the
interview you succeeded this interview
to me did not make me
necessarily like Amanda more I've always
liked Amanda I've always thought Amanda
was smart funny
um this interview did make
me understand you more a little bit more
but it made me think about how have
these other people experienced you I've
been in various group chats Amanda
steals has come up so many times that a
lot of the industry stuff I'm going
going to and I've heard stories from
people who have experienced
Amanda
and their experiences were not pleasant
however it was always the conclusion
that in spite of that it's still not
right to see you get piled on the way
these Publications piled up on you but
it makes it hard to defend you when you
continuously
self
sabotage it makes it hard for people to
defend you it
does
when you go on like when you go on this
interview and you you you you you speak
on Isa in a way
that that caused so much dangerous
Discord in a manner that we have never
seen with
Issa ever
it just makes it hard it makes it hard
to defend you and you know what Amanda
steel is probably somewhere like I don't
give a [ __ ] don't defend me which is
fine which is fine then don't ever come
online again and talk about how nobody
likes you these Publications don't
invite you
anywhere don't ever do that again ever
now is a time for you to figure out what
you're going to do on your own I don't
see Amanda working in Hollywood after
this I think Amanda would have to come
forward with a bombass standup like you
would have to drop the most fire ass
standup comedy special we've ever seen
or you'd have to get a placement in a
movie or a television role television
show role where you undeniably are
phenomenal and you leave everyone
breathless I don't see that happening so
however because Amanda is a podcaster a
radio show host she makes content she's
an activist I see Amanda just doing her
own thing do your own thing Amanda Do
Your Own Thing become your own
Outlet become your own Outlet um the
last thing I will speak on to is going
back to the empathy
thing that Tamir rice
segment was
horrible it was
horrible and I'm not going to do too
much on it actually I'mma let my friend
king of reads break it down some years
ago let me read the the the message
because it was originally on Instagram
where she commented so Samir rice Tamir
Rice mother posted this on Instagram and
she basically called Al Sean King why do
you think it's important to tell folks
we had a conversation well we talked and
everything was said was very toxic and
uncomfortable for me to hear that you
raised additional money and then said
you did not want to bother me personally
I don't understand how you sleep at
night I never gave you permission to
raise nothing along the United States
you robbed me for the D of my son you
gave me a cop and donut conversation all
lies Sean please stop thinking we on the
same page as a white man acting black
you are an impostor that cannot be
trusted my son 12 years old and doj
needs to reopen his case period to me
Human Rights was violated why would you
soever make it about you you are a
selfish self-centered person and God
will deal with you white man and this
was posted on you know Instagram and
Amanda seals you know posted this on the
blog um who reposted it and she said
this it's no secret that I have s i
meaning Sean King however bigger picture
nobody finds it someone odd that she
just out the blue going out of her way
and being given every platform with no
receipts shown to call out one by one
black activist SL organizers that have
been the visible faces of the movement
just Food For Thoughts Amanda seals
being a
Wordsmith understanding language all of
the things this is her response to a
mother who lost her
child this is her response there's no
Grace there's no care care there's no
anything Amanda seals is basically doing
everything to everybody else that she's
claiming folks are doing to her I could
never
imagine getting
online and coming for a grieving
mother in the
defense of
Sean talk Max
king of
Sean I just became a Muslim yesterday
let me sell y'all these Ramadan dinner
tickets
King okay of Sean croissant lval King I
could never do it that alone and Amanda
set herself on the podcast she don't
[ __ ] with Sean King like that so to
watch
you come for that that young
man's mother who
was
grieving and for you not to have empathy
to say you know what this is what I was
conveying I'm really really sorry I want
to take the time out to tell Tamir
Rice's mother that I apologize for
that that little generic apology that
you say oh if I've ever offended anybody
I'm sorry nah that's that's not going to
[ __ ]
work that's not going to [ __ ]
work Shannon didn't even ask you about
Tam rights you know why because he's not
well vered he don't he had no idea I
don't think Shannon sharp knew anything
about you prior to this interview
nothing but what he saw
online okay but had you been sitting
down with someone who was well vered in
the movement and well vered in what
happened with Tamir rice they would have
asked you so do you have anything that
you want to say to that man's
mother anything you want to clear
up and if you had no intentions to
apologize to that lady you should never
brought her
up Amanda you look for empathy in people
and you don't have it you don't have it
and that's really strange cuz you're a
cancer like me you're a cancer like me
like we're very empathetic to the point
where we be Tak taking up other people's
battles like and that's something that
I've had to stop doing like let me stop
let me stop you know every battle ain't
for me okay that battle is the Lord's
okay what you going through give it to
the Lord not me right but just watching
you just be so
unempathetic to that lady it just
was this interview to me was cringe the
entire interview was
cringe the entire interview was cringe I
don't know what the goal of this
was and I don't see much positivity
coming from this interview you've made
it very clear that you hate the
interview that you hate sh that you
don't that you felt that Shannon sharp
was interrogating
you it is what it is at this point um I
wish Amanda Seal's the best I text her I
asked her Hey listen like if you're ever
doing a show in Atlanta I would love to
you know honor two people uh from my uh
YouTube with tickets to your show so I'm
committed to doing that she didn't
answer I'm pretty sure her phone is
blown up um but I've been publicly very
supportive of her I still support her
but I got to be honest and say this was
a [ __ ] show it was a [ __ ] show like the
interview was one piece but your
behavior afterwards it just was I can't
I can't my sister has burned too many
britches and there's nothing I can do
for her um all right y'all well let me
know your thoughts I know this is
probably a long one but drop that in the
comments let me know your thoughts on uh
the Amanda seals interview and um I'll
see you guys in the next one take care